Guide to the Archives Information File, Section 4: Boxes 67-88
Archives Information File, Section 4: Boxes 67-88
- Box: 81, Folder: 32, Publication (Box 81, Folder 32)
  - Item 10: Glossary of Training Terms, Publication (Box 81, Folder 32)
    Author: Great Britain Ministry of Labor
  - Item 11: Issues in Training, Publication (Box 81, Folder 32)
  - Item 12: Need to Enhance the Effectiveness of On-the-Job Training in Appalachian Tennessee, 1970; Publication (Box 81, Folder 32)
    Notes: November 13, 1970
  - Item 13: The Psychodynamics of an Inter-Group Experience, Publication (Box 81, Folder 32)
    Author: Gurth Higgin & Harold Bridger
- Box: 81, Folder: 33, Publication (Box 81, Folder 33)
  - Item 1: On-the-Job Training, Publication (Box 81, Folder 33)
  - Item 2: Selecting and Training the Training Officer, Publication (Box 81, Folder 33)
    Author: Nancy Taylor
  - Item 3: British Industrial Research Associations, 1966; Publication (Box 81, Folder 33)
    Author: Committee of Directors of Research Associations
    Notes: November 16, 1966
  - Item 4: On-the-Job Training, Publication (Box 81, Folder 33)
  - Item 5: On-the-Job Training Programs, 1966; Publication (Box 81, Folder 33)
    Notes: March 31, 1966
  - Item 6: Organizing and Administering an Employee Training Program, Publication (Box 81, Folder 33)
    Author: Homer T. Rosenberger
  - Item 7: Public and Private Responsibilities in On-the-Job Training of Disadvantaged Workers, 1968; Publication (Box 81, Folder 33)
  - Item 8: Opportunities for Improving the Institutional Manpower Training Program in South Carolina, 1972; Publication (Box 81, Folder 33)
    Notes: April 11, 1972
  - Item 9: Report of Commission of Inquiry into Vocational Training, 1965; Publication (Box 81, Folder 33)
    Author: Commission of Inquiry into Vocational Training
  - Item 10: Research Training in Radiology, 1971; Publication (Box 81, Folder 33)
    Author: National Institute of General Medical Sciences
- Box: 82, Folder: 1, Publication (Box 82, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Training Disadvantaged Groups, 1963; Publication (Box 82, Folder 1)
  - Item 2: The Technical Assistance Training Program in Education, 1963; Publication (Box 82, Folder 1)
  - Item 3: Traning Rank-and-File Employees, 1962; Publication (Box 82, Folder 1)
    Notes: July 1962
  - Item 4: Training in Local Authorities, Publication (Box 82, Folder 1)
  - Item 5: Training for Labour Market Reasons, 1968; Publication (Box 82, Folder 1)
    Author: National Labour Market Board
  - Item 6: Training Employees, 1969; Publication (Box 82, Folder 1)
    Notes: November 1969
  - Item 7: Training Programs, Publication (Box 82, Folder 1)
  - Item 8: Training of Public Assistance Recipients Under the MDTA, 1966; Publication (Box 82, Folder 1)
  - Item 9: Training the Hard-Core Unemployed, Publication (Box 82, Folder 1)
  - Item 10: Workers in American Industry, Publication (Box 82, Folder 1)
  - Item 11: The Training Specialist in Industry, 1964; Publication (Box 82, Folder 1)
    Author: Industrial Training Council
  - Item 12: Training Can Make a Difference, 1974; Publication (Box 82, Folder 1)
    Notes: November 1974
  - Item 13: Training of Training Officers, Publication (Box 82, Folder 1)
  - Item 14: Training of Training Officers, Publication (Box 82, Folder 1)
- Box: 82, Folder: 2, Publication (Box 82, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Vocational Training Schemes for Industry, Publication (Box 82, Folder 2)
  - Item 2: Una Decada Al Servicio De Colombia, 1967; Publication (Box 82, Folder 2)
  - Item 3: The Role of Instructor in Business and Industry, Publication (Box 82, Folder 2)
    Author: Charles C. Denova
  - Item 4: Training, Publication (Box 82, Folder 2)
  - Item 5: Work and Training Provisions, 1971; Publication (Box 82, Folder 2)
    Notes: July 23, 1971
- Box: 82, Folder: 3, Publication (Box 82, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Training in the Aircraft Industry, 1957; Publication (Box 82, Folder 3)
    Notes: September 1957
- Box: 82, Folder: 4, Publication (Box 82, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: The Recruitment and Training of Automobile Mechanics, Publication (Box 82, Folder 4)
- Box: 82, Folder: 5, Publication (Box 82, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Industrial Training, 1969; Publication (Box 82, Folder 5)
    Author: Wigan and District Mining and Technical College
- Box: 82, Folder: 6, Publication (Box 82, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Building Custodian, Publication (Box 82, Folder 6)
- Box: 82, Folder: 7, Publication (Box 82, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Some Dimensions of the Drop-Out Problem in Apprenticeship Training, 1967; Publication (Box 82, Folder 7)
    Author: New Brunswick Department of Labour
- Box: 82, Folder: 8, Publication (Box 82, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: Interagency Training Programs, 1961; Publication (Box 82, Folder 8)
    Notes: Spring 1961
- Box: 82, Folder: 9, Publication (Box 82, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: Trade Unionism Among Public Servants in Ceylon, 1947; Publication (Box 82, Folder 9)
    Author: Ceylon Government
    Notes: February 1947
  - Item 2: Report on Apprenticeship Training, 1947; Publication (Box 82, Folder 9)
    Notes: September 1947
- Box: 82, Folder: 10, Publication (Box 82, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: Informe al Gobierno de Chile sobre la Formacion Profesional Agricola, 1963; Publication (Box 82, Folder 10)
    Author: Oficina Internacional del Trabajo
- Box: 82, Folder: 11, Publication (Box 82, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: Post-Entry Training in the Public Service in Western Europe, 1962; Publication (Box 82, Folder 11)
    Author: The International City Managers' Association
  - Item 2: Civil Service Commission Training Activities, 1965; Publication (Box 82, Folder 11)
    Author: U.S. Committee on Government Operations
    Notes: September 21, 1965
  - Item 3: Report Covering the Effectiveness of Implementation, 1967; Publication (Box 82, Folder 11)
    Notes: June 1, 1967
  - Item 4: Skills, Scholarship and the Public Service, Publication (Box 82, Folder 11)
  - Item 5: A Federal Staff College: A Report of a Panel Discussion, 1966; Publication (Box 82, Folder 11)
    Author: Federal Professional Association
- Box: 82, Folder: 12, Publication (Box 82, Folder 12)
  - Item 1: How to Hold a Meeting, Publication (Box 82, Folder 12)
    Author: Glenn L. Gardiner
  - Item 2: A Guide to Successful Conference Leadership, 1948; Publication (Box 82, Folder 12)
  - Item 3: Conference Leader Training Manual, 1943; Publication (Box 82, Folder 12)
    Author: New Jersey Department of Public Instruction
    Notes: June 1, 1943
  - Item 4: Ability to Lead Discussion Groups, 1940; Publication (Box 82, Folder 12)
    Notes: May 1940
  - Item 5: Two Lessons of Group Dynamics, Publication (Box 82, Folder 12)
    Author: Educator's Washington Dispatch
  - Item 6: Don't Let Your Conferences Bog Down, 1949; Publication (Box 82, Folder 12)
    Author: Alfred M Cooper
    Notes: August 1949
  - Item 7: Conference Sense, Publication (Box 82, Folder 12)
    Author: U.S. Navy
- Box: 82, Folder: 13, Publication (Box 82, Folder 13)
  - Item 1: How to Get More Out of Training Conferences, Publication (Box 82, Folder 13)
    Author: Harold P. Zelko
  - Item 2: Group Relations Training, 1960; Publication (Box 82, Folder 13)
    Notes: July 14, 1960
- Box: 82, Folder: 14, Publication (Box 82, Folder 14)
  - Item 1: New Careers in Private Industry, 1968; Publication (Box 82, Folder 14)
    Author: New York Chamber of Commerce
  - Item 2: Industrial Training: Whose Responsibility?, 1963; Publication (Box 82, Folder 14)
    Author: British Association for Commercial and Industrial Education
    Notes: January 15, 1963
- Box: 82, Folder: 15, Publication (Box 82, Folder 15)
  - Item 1: Education, Work, and Management, 1949; Publication (Box 82, Folder 15)
- Box: 82, Folder: 16, Publication (Box 82, Folder 16)
  - Item 1: Industrial Scholarships and Training Schemes, Publication (Box 82, Folder 16)
    Author: ACE Educational Booklets
- Box: 82, Folder: 17, Publication (Box 82, Folder 17)
  - Item 1: The Prediction of Outcomes of MDTA Programs, Publication (Box 82, Folder 17)
    Author: Performance Research
  - Item 2: Opportunities for improving Training Results and Efficiency at the East Bay Skills Center, 1971; Publication (Box 82, Folder 17)
    Notes: February 10, 1971
  - Item 3: Earnings Mobility of MDTA Trainees, 1967; Publication (Box 82, Folder 17)
  - Item 4: Operational Analysis of Training Programs, 1965; Publication (Box 82, Folder 17)
    Author: George Strauss
    Notes: May 26, 1965
  - Item 5: AD 609 605, Publication (Box 82, Folder 17)
  - Item 6: New Careers, Publication (Box 82, Folder 17)
    Author: Fred Powledge
  - Item 7: The Training of Young People in Industry, Publication (Box 82, Folder 17)
    Author: IWS
  - Item 8: Manpower Development and Training, Publication (Box 82, Folder 17)
  - Item 9: Administration and Effectiveness of Work Experience and Training Project, 1969; Publication (Box 82, Folder 17)
    Notes: July 31, 1969
  - Item 10: Administration and Effectiveness of Work Experience and Training Project, 1969; Publication (Box 82, Folder 17)
    Notes: May 26, 1969
  - Item 11: Manpower Training Facts, 1965; Publication (Box 82, Folder 17)
  - Item 12: Report of the U.S. Committee on Administration of Training Programs, 1968; Publication (Box 82, Folder 17)
    Author: U.S. Committee on Administration of Training Programs
  - Item 13: Criteria and Guidelines for the Evaluation of In-Service Training, Publication (Box 82, Folder 17)
  - Item 14: Characteristics of Graduates and Dropouts from Government-Sponsored On-the-Job Training Programmes, Publication (Box 82, Folder 17)
- Box: 82, Folder: 18, Publication (Box 82, Folder 18)
  - Item 1: Executive Development Programs at Universities, 1958; Publication (Box 82, Folder 18)
    Notes: August 1958
  - Item 2: The Development of Executive Talent, 1928; Publication (Box 82, Folder 18)
    Author: W.W. Charters
    Notes: February 9, 1928
  - Item 3: Education for Management, 1947; Publication (Box 82, Folder 18)
    Author: Great Britain Ministry of Education
  - Item 4: Industry and Education Meet a Training Challenge, 1948; Publication (Box 82, Folder 18)
    Author: Walter B. Lovelace
  - Item 5: Organizing and Developing the Management Team, Publication (Box 82, Folder 18)
  - Item 6: Management Education, Publication (Box 82, Folder 18)
    Author: S.A.M. Committee on Relations with Colleges and Universities
  - Item 7: The Staff College in Training for Management, Publication (Box 82, Folder 18)
  - Item 8: A New Look at Management Development, Publication (Box 82, Folder 18)
    Author: Leland P. Bradford
  - Item 9: Training College Graduates for Management, Publication (Box 82, Folder 18)
  - Item 10: Management Development: Case Studies, Publication (Box 82, Folder 18)
- Box: 82, Folder: 19, Publication (Box 82, Folder 19)
  - Item 1: Development of Managerial Performance, 1963; Publication (Box 82, Folder 19)
    Author: South-Western Publishing Co.
  - Item 2: Development of a Body of Management Teachers, 1962; Publication (Box 82, Folder 19)
- Box: 82, Folder: 20, Publication (Box 82, Folder 20)
  - Item 1: Executive Training and Development, 1964; Publication (Box 82, Folder 20)
    Author: California Institute of Technology
    Notes: February 1964
  - Item 2: Exetending Managerial Competence, 1968; Publication (Box 82, Folder 20)
    Author: Mel H. Bolster
  - Item 3: Executive Training in Department Stores, 1952; Publication (Box 82, Folder 20)
    Author: Donald K. Beckley
- Box: 82, Folder: 21, Publication (Box 82, Folder 21)
  - Item 1: The Quest for Leadership and Excellence, 1966; Publication (Box 82, Folder 21)
    Author: Virgil B. Day
    Notes: August 10, 1966
- Box: 82, Folder: 22, Publication (Box 82, Folder 22)
  - Item 1: Self-Development: A New Emphasis in Management Training, Publication (Box 82, Folder 22)
    Author: Charles Sener, Max Clark
  - Item 2: Management Development within the Firm, 1959; Publication (Box 82, Folder 22)
  - Item 3: Executive Development, 1967; Publication (Box 82, Folder 22)
  - Item 4: Management Trainee Programs, 1963; Publication (Box 82, Folder 22)
  - Item 5: Building a Management Development Program Through Planning and Controls, Publication (Box 82, Folder 22)
    Author: Preston P. Le Breton
  - Item 6: Administrative Management Courses, 1961; Publication (Box 82, Folder 22)
- Box: 82, Folder: 23, Publication (Box 82, Folder 23)
  - Item 1: Training and Development of Managers Further Proposals, Publication (Box 82, Folder 23)
    Author: Great Britain Department of Employment and Productivity
  - Item 2: University-Sponsored Executive Developments Programs in the Public Service, Publication (Box 82, Folder 23)
    Author: Ward Stewart
  - Item 3: Tomorrow's Executive - Educated for Change, Publication (Box 82, Folder 23)
  - Item 4: What an Executive Should Know About Managing Time Effectively, Publication (Box 82, Folder 23)
    Author: Ray Josephs
- Box: 82, Folder: 24, Publication (Box 82, Folder 24)
  - Item 1: Evaluation of Management Training and Development Programs, Publication (Box 82, Folder 24)
    Author: Vera Kohn
- Box: 82, Folder: 25, Publication (Box 82, Folder 25)
  - Item 1: Practicing Supervision, Publication (Box 82, Folder 25)
  - Item 2: Training in Supervision and Management, Publication (Box 82, Folder 25)
    Author: A.M.B. Rule, D.H. Bramley
  - Item 3: Selection & Training of Supervisors, Publication (Box 82, Folder 25)
  - Item 4: Better Supervision, Publication (Box 82, Folder 25)
    Author: U.S. Office of Production Management
  - Item 5: Supervisory Training, Publication (Box 82, Folder 25)
    Author: Associated Industrial Relations Institute
  - Item 6: Foreman Training Plans, Publication (Box 82, Folder 25)
- Box: 83, Folder: 1, Publication (Box 83, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: An Analysis and Inventory of the Skills of Management and Supervision, 1963; Publication (Box 83, Folder 1)
    Author: Federal Aviation Agency
  - Item 2: Employee Conduct, 1964; Publication (Box 83, Folder 1)
  - Item 3: How a Temple University Survey Shows Relationship of Supervisory Attitudes with Training Practices, Publication (Box 83, Folder 1)
- Box: 83, Folder: 2, Publication (Box 83, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Getting Started at Supervisory Training, 1965; Publication (Box 83, Folder 2)
    Author: Jerry J. Jensen
  - Item 2: Management Training by the Line Organization, 1962; Publication (Box 83, Folder 2)
    Author: Robert N. Coe
  - Item 3: Job Instruction Training, Publication (Box 83, Folder 2)
    Author: Ouachita Valley Vocational-Technical School
  - Item 4: Job Instruction Training, Publication (Box 83, Folder 2)
  - Item 5: How 152 Companies Train Foremen, Publication (Box 83, Folder 2)
- Box: 83, Folder: 3, Publication (Box 83, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Selection and Training of Supervisors, Especially in Small and Medium-Sized Firms, 1970; Publication (Box 83, Folder 3)
  - Item 2: The Significance of Training Design in Developing Supervisors, Publication (Box 83, Folder 3)
    Author: Victor W. Hodapp
  - Item 3: The Substance of Supervisory Training, Publication (Box 83, Folder 3)
    Author: Siegmar F. Blamberg
  - Item 4: The Art of Supervision, 1964; Publication (Box 83, Folder 3)
- Box: 83, Folder: 4, Publication (Box 83, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Supervisory Training: Case Studies, Publication (Box 83, Folder 4)
- Box: 83, Folder: 5, Publication (Box 83, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Supervisory Training, Publication (Box 83, Folder 5)
  - Item 2: The Training of Supervisors, Publication (Box 83, Folder 5)
    Author: Engineering Industry Training Board
- Box: 83, Folder: 6, Publication (Box 83, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Handbook for Instructors in Management Programs, Publication (Box 83, Folder 6)
  - Item 2: How to Train Workers on the Job, Publication (Box 83, Folder 6)
- Box: 83, Folder: 7, Publication (Box 83, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: The Guide to Training and the Future, 1972; Publication (Box 83, Folder 7)
    Author: G.Terry Page
- Box: 83, Folder: 8, Publication (Box 83, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: Educational & Technical Training Requirements of Production Process Workers in Tanneries, 1961; Publication (Box 83, Folder 8)
    Author: India National Employment Service
    Notes: August 1961
- Box: 83, Folder: 9, Publication (Box 83, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: Survey of Library Technician Training Courses in Alberta, British Columbia, Manitoba and Ontario, 1968; Publication (Box 83, Folder 9)
    Author: Marion C. Wilson, June E. Munro
  - Item 2: On-the-Job Training of Library Personnel, 1968; Publication (Box 83, Folder 9)
    Notes: May 31, 1968
- Box: 83, Folder: 10, Publication (Box 83, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: Training of Dock Workers in Great Britain, 1966; Publication (Box 83, Folder 10)
    Author: Great Britain National Dock Labour Board
- Box: 83, Folder: 11, Publication (Box 83, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: Recruiting and Training Labor for Woods Work, 1949; Publication (Box 83, Folder 11)
    Author: Fred C. Simmons
    Notes: April 1949
- Box: 83, Folder: 12, Publication (Box 83, Folder 12)
  - Item 1: Training of Maintenance Workers, 1967; Publication (Box 83, Folder 12)
    Author: International Labour Office
- Box: 83, Folder: 13, Publication (Box 83, Folder 13)
  - Item 1: Training Health Service Workers: The Critical Challenge, 1966; Publication (Box 83, Folder 13)
    Notes: February 14-17, 1966
- Box: 83, Folder: 14, Publication (Box 83, Folder 14)
  - Item 1: Medical Laboratory Assistant, Publication (Box 83, Folder 14)
- Box: 83, Folder: 15, Publication (Box 83, Folder 15)
  - Item 1: Sheet Metal Industry, 1965; Publication (Box 83, Folder 15)
- Box: 83, Folder: 16, Publication (Box 83, Folder 16)
  - Item 1: Proven Management Aids, Publication (Box 83, Folder 16)
  - Item 2: Parameters Affecting the Relative Efficiency of Part and Whole Training Methods, 1962; Publication (Box 83, Folder 16)
    Author: James C. Naylor
    Notes: February 18, 1962
- Box: 83, Folder: 17, Publication (Box 83, Folder 17)
  - Item 1: Role Strains and Adaption in a Multidisciplinary Group Teaching Unit, Publication (Box 83, Folder 17)
    Author: Bernard Schoenberg, Jay Schulman
- Box: 83, Folder: 18, Publication (Box 83, Folder 18)
  - Item 1: Industrial Retraining Programs for Technological Change, Publication (Box 83, Folder 18)
  - Item 2: Training, 1971; Publication (Box 83, Folder 18)
  - Item 3: Training the Adult Worker, Publication (Box 83, Folder 18)
    Author: Eunice Belbin
- Box: 83, Folder: 19, Publication (Box 83, Folder 19)
  - Item 1: Using Gimmicks to "Sell" Training Programs, Publication (Box 83, Folder 19)
- Box: 83, Folder: 20, Publication (Box 83, Folder 20)
  - Item 1: Educational and Technical Training Requirements of Production Process Workers, 1961; Publication (Box 83, Folder 20)
- Box: 83, Folder: 21, Publication (Box 83, Folder 21)
  - Item 1: Syllabus for Police Supervisory Training, Publication (Box 83, Folder 21)
- Box: 83, Folder: 22, Publication (Box 83, Folder 22)
  - Item 1: Criteria for Technician Education, 1968; Publication (Box 83, Folder 22)
- Box: 83, Folder: 23, Publication (Box 83, Folder 23)
  - Item 1: Increasing Team Proficiency Throught Training, 1960; Publication (Box 83, Folder 23)
    Author: David J. Klaus & Robert Glaser
  - Item 2: Training Research, 1957; Publication (Box 83, Folder 23)
    Notes: February 1957
- Box: 83, Folder: 24, Publication (Box 83, Folder 24)
  - Item 1: Research Needed in Industrial Training, 1950; Publication (Box 83, Folder 24)
- Box: 83, Folder: 25, Publication (Box 83, Folder 25)
  - Item 1: Retail Staff Training, Publication (Box 83, Folder 25)
    Author: Janet B. Marcham
  - Item 2: Training Chain Store Personnel, Publication (Box 83, Folder 25)
- Box: 83, Folder: 26, Publication (Box 83, Folder 26)
  - Item 1: Sales Training and Direction, Publication (Box 83, Folder 26)
    Author: S.D. Warren Company
  - Item 2: Training Salesmen, Publication (Box 83, Folder 26)
- Box: 83, Folder: 27, Publication (Box 83, Folder 27)
  - Item 1: Recruiting and Training Employees in the Service Industries, Publication (Box 83, Folder 27)
- Box: 83, Folder: 28, Publication (Box 83, Folder 28)
  - Item 1: Steward Training, Publication (Box 83, Folder 28)
    Author: Mildred Bersh
  - Item 2: Training Shop Stewards, Publication (Box 83, Folder 28)
- Box: 83, Folder: 29, Publication (Box 83, Folder 29)
  - Item 1: Training for Small Manufacturing Enterprises in Developing Countries, 1967; Publication (Box 83, Folder 29)
    Notes: May 26, 1967
- Box: 83, Folder: 30, Publication (Box 83, Folder 30)
  - Item 1: Training for Social Work in Africa, 1964; Publication (Box 83, Folder 30)
- Box: 83, Folder: 31, Publication (Box 83, Folder 31)
  - Item 1: Training in the British Iron and Steel Industry, Publication (Box 83, Folder 31)
    Author: British Steel Corporation
- Box: 83, Folder: 32, Publication (Box 83, Folder 32)
  - Item 1: Educational and Technical Training Requirements of Production Process Workers in the Cotton Textile Industry, 1961; Publication (Box 83, Folder 32)
- Box: 83, Folder: 33, Publication (Box 83, Folder 33)
  - Item 1: Opportunities for Improving Training Results and Efficiency at the East Bay Skills Center, 1971; Publication (Box 83, Folder 33)
  - Item 2: Making Effective Use of Long-Term Training, 1973; Publication (Box 83, Folder 33)
    Notes: October 1973
  - Item 3: Safety is Part of Our Job, Publication (Box 83, Folder 33)
    Author: Anaconda Wire & Cable Company
- Box: 83, Folder: 34, Publication (Box 83, Folder 34)
  - Item 1: Employee Training for Better Public Service, 1960; Publication (Box 83, Folder 34)
- Box: 83, Folder: 35, Publication (Box 83, Folder 35)
  - Item 1: Help for Out-of-Work Youth, Publication (Box 83, Folder 35)
    Author: National Child Labor Committee
  - Item 2: Job Corps Conservation Centers Program, 1964; Publication (Box 83, Folder 35)
    Author: U.S. Office of Economic Opportunity
    Notes: August 20, 1964
  - Item 3: Amendments to the Manpower Development and Training Act, Publication (Box 83, Folder 35)
  - Item 4: Youth Training and Employment Programs, Publication (Box 83, Folder 35)
    Author: New York Community Service Society
  - Item 5: Job Corps Centers for Women, Publication (Box 83, Folder 35)
  - Item 6: Getting Hired, Getting Trained, Publication (Box 83, Folder 35)
  - Item 7: Getting Hired, Getting Trained, Publication (Box 83, Folder 35)
  - Item 8: Youth Opportunity Campaign, 1967; Publication (Box 83, Folder 35)
    Notes: Summer 1967
- Box: 83, Folder: 36, Publication (Box 83, Folder 36)
  - Item 1: Training Girls in Industry, 1962; Publication (Box 83, Folder 36)
    Notes: November 1962
- Box: 83, Folder: 37, Publication (Box 83, Folder 37)
  - Item 1: Training for New Careers, 1965; Publication (Box 83, Folder 37)
    Author: President's Committee on Juvenile Delinquency and Youth Crime
- Box: 83, Folder: 38, Publication (Box 83, Folder 38)
  - Item 1: An Evaluation of the Seattle Opportunities Industrialization Center, Publication (Box 83, Folder 38)
    Author: Richard B. Peterson
- Box: 83, Folder: 39, Publication (Box 83, Folder 39)
  - Item 1: A Community Plan for Service to Transients, Publication (Box 83, Folder 39)
- Box: 83, Folder: 40, Publication (Box 83, Folder 40)
  - Item 1: Transportation Facts & Trends, 1966; Publication (Box 83, Folder 40)
    Author: Transportation Association of America
  - Item 2: Dilemma: People in Motion, 1965; Publication (Box 83, Folder 40)
    Author: Leslie B. Worthington
    Notes: August 10, 1965
  - Item 3: The Business Logistics to Transportation and Distribution, 1965; Publication (Box 83, Folder 40)
  - Item 4: Dynamic Transport Policies for a Dynamic America, Publication (Box 83, Folder 40)
- Box: 83, Folder: 41, Publication (Box 83, Folder 41)
  - Item 1: Road Passenger Transport in Britain, 1965; Publication (Box 83, Folder 41)